

PROFILE

I offer 4 years of experience in development, currently working as a Software Engineer in Coventry UK.

My goal is to keep growing my career as a Full-Stack Software Engineer.

Coding is my passion, I am highly motivated, focused, with a lot of will to keep learning.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+44 7448719858

EMAIL:

atanasskambitovv@gmail.com

LINKS

GitHub:

https://github.com/NASOKILA

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/atanaskambitov-a69528162/

LANGUAGES

English | Italian | Spanish | Bulgarian

DIPLOMAS & CERTIFICATES

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Diplomas-Certificates

ATANAS KAMBITOV

Software Engineer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sainsbury's Store | Software Engineer | Coventry UK

03/12/2018 - Now (7 months)

Hands on experience with Microservice architecture and full-stack development including unit, integration and performance testing. Experience in Docker and Azure services - DevOps, SignalR, Key vault, AAD, Redis, Container Registry, Kubernetes, App Service, Azure Cosmos, Service Bus, Event Hub, Stream analytics and more.

Working in an agile way with scrum in a team of five people providing code quality, latency, stability and performance.

A lot of work with .Net Core, React, non-relational and SQL databases.

SoftUni | Software Engineer | Sofia, Bulgaria

05/12/2016 - 21/12/2018 (2 years)

Create and maintain backend API's, databases and frontend apps. Quickly deliver quality code and meet deadlines in a high pressure work environment with deferent technologies, languages and frameworks.

Paolo Pavia | Prestashop & WordPress Developer | Sofia, Bulgaria

11/02/2015 – 19/05/2016 (1 year and 3 months)

Develop, support and rebuild cloud based applications related to shopping, advertisement and promotion.

Successfully increase sales and client traffic on our applications.

EDUCATION

South-West University "Neofit Rilski"

15/09/2014 - 25/05/2018 (4 years) Bachelor degree in Informatics.

Private Software University (SoftUni)

05/12/2016 - 21/12/2018 (2 years)

Professionally graduated and qualified C# and JavaScript developer.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Agile Methodologies | Azure Services | Kubernetes | GitHub | Docker Microservices | REST API | .NET Core | .Net Framework | React.js | SQL Redux | Angular | Typescript | Vue.js | JavaScript | Mongo DB HTML5 & CSS3 | JQuery | Less & Sass | Bootstrap | Node.js

PERSONAL PROJECTS

.Net Core

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Tangy-Restaurant

Angular

https://nasokila.github.io/comix-shop/

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Portfolio-Projects/tree/comix-shop

React.is

https://nasokila.github.io/house-shop/

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Portfolio-Projects/tree/house-shop